how do you feel about the report I feel
confident about the numbers I feel like
I want some ice cream but not the whole
pint just like a little bite you know
what I mean you should try share your
eats yeah big dog Jerry just spent 27.99
to get this delivered and barely a half
what is this share your eats as a food
delivery app designed to connect
like-minded Foodies and end world hunger
one lose Fry at a time you can go
or lift line share your eats will bring
your half craving to your door in about
12 to 48 minutes dude that took two
hours with taxes surcharges tips and
fees food delivery can be expensive plus
it's already cold when it gets to you
anyway
there you are it's been forever
before placing your order we have to
connect
that was fast
so why not split your meal with a
company stranger and cut your costs and
calories in half on top of saving money
users can earn rewards by letting us
know where there's extra food in their
area
Thank you Grandma now instead of
scraping sesame seeds off your bun you
can just opt for the bottom half of a
burger but how do they get it so even
and juicy on top of highly trained
drivers our technology connects users
based on their preferences
[Music]
I always knew that he was about him
also allows drivers to scan for E coli
[Music]
don't forget to rate and tip your
drivers generously
share your eats last week's food today
what's up guys I'm Andrew Bowie while
you're sharing those eats don't forget
to share this video and also like
comment and subscribe love you guys see
you on the next one
[Music]